Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Northacres Park - Contracts Agreements, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 41/24)
  - Northacres Park - Financial, 1971 (Box-folder 41/25)
  - (Northeast Queen Anne) Mayfair Park - Contracts Agreements, 1973 (Box-folder 42/1)
  - (Northeast Queen Anne) Mayfair Park, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 42/2)
  - (Northeast Queen Anne) Mayfair Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 42/3)
  - (Northeast Queen Anne) Mayfair Viewpoint, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 42/4)
  - Northeast 80th St. Viewpoint, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 42/5)
  - Northwest Center for the Retarded, 1975 (Box-folder 42/6)
  - Northwest Center for the Retarded, 1976 (Box-folder 42/7)
  - Occidental Park, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 42/8)
  - Occidental Square Park, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 42/9)
  - Occidental Square Park Agreements, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 42/10)
  - Occidental Park, 1972 (Box-folder 42/11)
  - Occidental Park, 1973 (Box-folder 42/12)
  - Occidental Park, 1974 (Box-folder 42/13)
  - Occidental Park - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 42/14)
  - Othello (Brighton) Playground, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 42/15)
  - Othello (Brighton) Playground, 1976 (Box-folder 42/16)
  - Othello (Brighton) Playground, 1977 (Box-folder 42/17)
  - Othello Playground, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 42/18)
  - Outdoor Basketball Courts, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 42/19)
  - Park Office Expansion, 1969 (Box-folder 42/20)
  - Phinney Ridge Play Area, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 42/21)
  - Pier 57/59 Renovation, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 42/22)
  - Pier 57/59 Substructure Renovation, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 42/23)
  - Pier 57/59 Substructure Renovation, 1983 (Box-folder 42/24)
  - Pier 57/59 Substructure Renovation, 1983 (Box-folder 42/25)
  - Pier 59 Concession Development, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 42/26)
  - Pier 59 Concession Development, 1979 (Box-folder 42/27)
  - Pier 59 Concession Development, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 42/28)
  - Pier 57/59 Substructure Renovation, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 43/1)
  - Pier 59 Concession Development, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 43/2)
  - Pier 59 Concession Development, 1983 (Box-folder 43/3)
  - Pier 61 Demolition, 1979 (Box-folder 43/4)
  - Pinehurst Playground Shelter, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 43/5)
  - Piling Replacement Project, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 43/6)
  - Pioneer Square Acquisition, 1970 (Box-folder 43/7)
  - Pioneer Square Occidental Parks, 1971 (Box-folder 43/8)
  - Pioneer Square Occidental Parks, 1971 (Box-folder 43/9)
  - Pioneer Square Rehabilitation, 1972 (Box-folder 43/10)
  - Pioneer Square, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 43/11)
  - Pioneer Square Rehabilitation, 1972 (Box-folder 43/12)
  - Pioneer Square Rehabilitation, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 43/13)
  - Pioneer Square Rehabilitation - Programming Planning, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 43/14)
  - Pioneer Square Rehabilitation - Planning Program, 1973 (Box-folder 43/15)
  - Pioneer Square - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 43/16)
  - Pioneer Square - Financial, 1972-1984 (Box-folder 43/17)
  - Playground Alki, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 43/18)
  - Playgrounds - Bobby Morris (Broadway), 1979-1982 (Box-folder 43/19)
  - Playgrounds - University, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 43/20)
  - Playgrounds - University, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 43/21)
  - Playground Improvements, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 43/22)
  - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 43/23)
  - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 43/24)
  - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 43/25)
  - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 43/26)
  - Prefontaine Fountain, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 43/27)
  - Pritchard Beach Island Gate, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 43/28)
  - Queen Anne Pool Site, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 44/1)
  - Queen Anne Pool Site, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44/2)
  - Queen Anne Pool Project Description, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 44/3)
  - Queen Anne Pool Committee, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44/4)
  - Queen Anne Pool, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 44/5)
  - Queen Anne Pool Environmental Impact Statement, 1973 (Box-folder 44/6)
  - Queen Anne Pool Environmental Assessment Addendum, 1973 (Box-folder 44/7)
  - Queen Anne Pool - Environmental Assessment Addendum, 1973 (Box-folder 44/8)
  - Queen Anne Pool Planning and Program, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 44/9)
  - Queen Anne Pool - Correspondence, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 44/10)
  - Queen Anne Swimming Pool Reports Studies, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 44/11)
  - Queen Anne Pool Financial, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 44/12)
  - Queen Anne Swimming Pool - Equipment, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 44/13)
  - Queen Anne Pool - newspaper clippings, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 44/14)
  - (Queen Anne Viewpoint) / Bhy Kracke Park, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 44/15)
  - (Queen Anne Viewpoint) / Bhy Kracke Park: Contracts and Agreements, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 44/16)
  - Queen Anne Hill Viewpoint Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 44/17)
  - Queen Anne Hill Viewpoint, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 44/18)
  - Queen Anne Hill Viewpoint Financial, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 44/19)
  - Pool Stairs, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 44/20)
  - Queen Anne Bowl, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 44/21)
  - Queen Anne Bowl Financial (includes slides), 1972 (Box-folder 44/22)
  - Queen Anne Park - Coe School, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 44/23)
  - Queen Anne Parks, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 44/24)
  - Racquetball, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 44/25)
  - Raft / Pier Replacement - Mt. Baker Seward Park, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 44/26)
  - Rainier Community Center Improvements CDBG, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Rainier Community Center Improvements, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 45/2)
  - Rainier Community Center Improvements, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 45/3)
  - Rainier Community Center Improvements - Construction Meeting Reports, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 45/4)
  - Rainier Community Center Improvements, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 45/5)
  - Rainier Playfield, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 45/6)
  - Rainier Playfield (includes aerial photographs), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 45/7)
  - Rainier Playfield, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 45/8)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, Pool, etc., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 45/9)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, Pool, Playground, 1970 (Box-folder 45/10)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 45/11)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center Pool Playground, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 45/12)
  - Rainier Beach Playfield and Swimming Pool Contract and Agreements, 1971 (Box-folder 45/13)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center and Pool - Agreements Contracts, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 45/14)
  - Rainier Beach Playfield Swimming Pool, 1971 (Box-folder 45/15)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, Pool, Playfield, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 45/16)
  - Rainer Beach Recreation Center - Construction, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 45/17)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, 1972 (Box-folder 45/18)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, 1972 (Box-folder 45/19)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center - Agreements, 1972 (Box-folder 45/20)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, 1972 (Box-folder 45/21)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center, Pool, Playfield, 1973 (Box-folder 45/22)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center and Pool, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 45/23)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center and Swimming Pool, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 45/24)
  - Rainier Beach (Southeast) Recreation Center, 1968 (Box-folder 46/1)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center (Southeast), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 46/2)
  - Rainier Beach Community Center Job -Site Meeting Reports, 1972 (Box-folder 46/3)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center: Job-Site Meeting Reports, 1973 (Box-folder 46/4)
  - Rainier Beach Community Center: Job-Site Meeting Reports, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 46/5)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center Pool - Dedication, 1974 (Box-folder 46/6)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center and Pool, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 46/7)
  - Rainier Beach - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 46/8)
  - Rainier Beach Community Center - Drawings, 1974 (Box-folder 46/9)
  - Rainier Beach Tennis Courts, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 46/10)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center - Legal Friesen Deposition, 1976 (Box-folder 46/11)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center - Legal, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 46/12)
  - Rainier Beach Recreation Center - Legal, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 46/13)
  - Rainier Beach and South Park Community Centers, 1976 (Box-folder 46/14)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 46/15)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements, 1977 (Box-folder 46/16)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements Project File Jan. - June, 1978 (Box-folder 46/17)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements Project File July - Dec., 1978 (Box-folder 46/18)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements: Project File, 1979 (Box-folder 46/19)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements: Project File, 1980 (Box-folder 46/20)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements: Project File, 1981 (Box-folder 46/21)
  - Ravenna Park Improvements: Project File, 1982 (Box-folder 46/22)
  - Ravenna Ravine Extension Project, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 46/23)
  - Ravenna Boulevard Improvements, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 46/24)
  - Ravenna Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 46/25)
  - Red Barn Ranch, 1971 (Box-folder 46/26)
  - Red Barn Ranch, 1972 (Box-folder 46/27)
  - Red Barn Ranch, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 46/28)
  - Red Barn Ranch, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 46/29)
  - Renovation and Maintenance Study, 1979 (Box-folder 47/1)
  - Renovation and Maintenance, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 47/2)
  - Renovation and Maintenance Study, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 47/3)
  - Renovation and Maintenance Study, 1980 (Box-folder 47/4)
  - Renovation and Maintenance Study, 1981 (Box-folder 47/5)
  - Riverview Playfield, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 47/6)
  - Riverview Pee Wee Restroom, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 47/7)
  - Riverview Playfield Irrigation, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 47/8)
  - Jose Rizal Park, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 47/9)
  - Jose Rizal Park - Design and Construction Contracts and Master Plan, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 47/10)
  - Jose Rizal Park, 1978 (Box-folder 47/11)
  - Jose Rizal Park, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 47/12)
  - Jose Rizal Park Variance, 1979 (Box-folder 47/13)
  - Jose Rizal Park, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 47/14)
  - Jose Rizal Park (Incl. Photographs), 1980-1981 (Box-folder 47/15)
  - Jose Rizal Park (Incl. Photographs), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 47/16)
  - David Rodgers Park, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 47/17)
  - Roofing Projects, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 47/18)
  - Ross Playground, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 47/19)
  - Roxhill Park Shelterhouse, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 47/20)
  - Roxhill Park Shelterhouse, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 47/21)
  - Roxhill Park Shelterhouse, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 47/22)
  - Sacajawea Playfield, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 48/1)
  - School Security, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 48/2)
  - Seacrest Marina, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 48/3)
  - Seacrest Marina, 1977 (Box-folder 48/4)
  - Seacrest Marina, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 48/5)
  - Seacrest Marina - Engineering Survey Report, 1981 (Box-folder 48/6)
  - Seacrest Marina, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 48/7)
  - Seacrest Marina Newspaper Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 48/8)
  - Stan Sayres Park, 1981 (Box-folder 48/9)
  - Seattle Art Museum Skylights, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 48/10)
  - Seattle Model City Program - Playgrounds, 1973 (Box-folder 48/11)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 48/12)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1972 (Box-folder 48/13)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1973 (Box-folder 48/14)
  - Seattle Tennis Center: Site Analysis, 1973 (Box-folder 48/15)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1973 (Box-folder 48/16)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1974 (Box-folder 48/17)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1975 (Box-folder 48/18)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1975 (Box-folder 48/19)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1975 (Box-folder 48/20)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1976 (Box-folder 48/21)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1976 (Box-folder 48/22)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1976 (Box-folder 48/23)
  - Seattle Tennis Center - Reports and Studies, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 49/1)
  - Seattle Tennis Center - Reports and Studies, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 49/2)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1975 (Box-folder 49/3)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 49/4)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1977 (Box-folder 49/5)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1977 (Box-folder 49/6)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1978 (Box-folder 49/7)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1978 (Box-folder 49/8)
  - Seattle Tennis Center, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 49/9)
  - Seattle Tennis Center - Contracts Agreements, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 49/10)
  - Seattle Tennis Center: Application for Federal Surplus Property (includes photographs), 1979 (Box-folder 49/11)
  - Seattle Tennis Center: Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 49/12)
  - Seattle Tennis Center - Hillside Stabilization / Fire Hydrants, 1980 (Box-folder 49/13)
  - Seattle Tennis Center Phase I Lighting, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 49/14)
  - Service Shops and Yards - Program Contracts, 1972 (Box-folder 49/15)
  - Service Shops and Yards, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 49/16)
  - Service Shops and Yards - Planning and Program, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 49/17)
  - Service Shops and Yards - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 49/18)
  - 17th Avenue Street Park, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 49/19)
  - Seward Park Sanitary Sewer, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 49/20)
  - Seward Park Sanitary Sewer - Federal Assistance, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 49/21)
  - Seward Park Sanitary Sewer, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 50/1)
  - Seward Park, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 50/2)
  - Seward Park - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 50/3)
  - Seward Park - Art Studio, 1974 (Box-folder 50/4)
  - Seward Park Improvements - Contracts Agreements, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 50/5)
  - Seward Park Improvements, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 50/6)
  - Seward Park Improvements, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 50/7)
  - Seward Park - Paving, 1979 (Box-folder 50/8)
  - Seward Park - Comfort Station Picnic Shelter Improvements: Contracts Agreements, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 50/9)
  - Seward Park - Comfort Station Picnic Shelter Improvements, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 50/10)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase I - Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 50/11)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase I: Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 50/12)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase I: Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 50/13)
  - Shoreline Improvements Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 50/14)
  - Shoreline Improvements Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 50/15)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase I - Construction Meeting Reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 50/16)
  - Shoreline Improvements: Seward Park / Ohler Island Contracts, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 50/17)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase I Seward Park / Ohler Island, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 50/18)
  - Shoreline Improvements Consultant Contract, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 50/19)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase II, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 50/20)
  - Shoreline Improvements Phase II, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 50/21)
  - Small Parks Recreation Areas, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 50/22)
  - Small Parks Recreation Areas, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 50/23)
  - Small Parks Recreation Areas, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/24)
  - Small Parks Recreation Areas, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 50/25)
  - Soundview Terrace, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 51/1)
  - S. College St. Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 51/2)
  - S. College St. Park - Correspondence (includes color slides), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/3)
  - South College St. Park, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 51/4)
  - South Lake Union Park, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 51/5)
  - South Park Fence, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 51/6)
  - South Park Playfield, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 51/7)
  - South Park Recreation Center - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 51/8)
  - South Park Recreation Center Rehabilitation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 51/9)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool - Program, 1972 (Box-folder 51/10)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 51/11)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool, 1974 (Box-folder 51/12)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 51/13)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool - Design Contract, 1973 (Box-folder 51/14)
  - Southwest Recreation Center Sealth Pool - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 51/15)
  - Spring Street Park (mini park), 1969-1971 (Box-folder 51/16)
  - Spruce Street Mini Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 51/17)
  - Spruce Street Mini Park - Land Acquisition, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 51/18)
  - Sports Field Improvements, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 51/19)
  - Sports Field Improvements, 1980 (Box-folder 51/20)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Interbay, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 51/21)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Nathan Hale High School, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 51/22)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Nathan Hale High School Phase II, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 51/23)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Lower Woodland Floodlights, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 51/24)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Lower Woodland Fence, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 51/25)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Lower Woodland, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 51/26)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Lower Woodland Playfield, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 51/27)
  - Sports Field Improvements - Meadow brook, 1968-1983 (Box-folder 51/28)
  - Sports Field - Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 51/29)
  - Swimming Pools - Background, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 52/1)
  - Swimming Pool Program, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 52/2)
  - Swimming Pool Improvements, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 52/3)
  - Swimming Pool Improvements, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 52/4)
  - Swimming Pool Improvements, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 52/5)
  - Swimming Pool Improvements - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 52/6)
  - Tashkent Park (Belmont Mini), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 52/7)
  - Tashkent Park (Belmont Mini Park), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 52/8)
  - Tashkent Park (Belmont Mini) - Contracts Agreements, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 52/9)
  - Tashkent Park (Belmont Mini Park) - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 52/10)
  - Tennis Court Project - Rogers Jefferson Rehab, 1979 (Box-folder 52/11)
  - Tennis Court Project - Planning Administration, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 52/12)
  - Tennis Court Project (CDBG), 1975 (Box-folder 52/13)
  - Tennis Court Project - Planning Administration, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 52/14)
  - Tennis Court Project - Rainier / Riverview / Rainier Beach, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 52/15)
  - Tennis Court Project - Rainier, Riverview, Rainier Beach, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 52/16)
  - Tennis Courts - Resurfacing Project, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 52/17)
  - Tennis Court Lighting, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 52/18)
  - Thirtieth Avenue Mini-Park / William Grose Park, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 52/19)
  - Thirtieth Avenue Mini-Park / William Grose Park, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 52/20)
  - 34th Pike Mini-Park, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 52/21)
  - Thirty-seventh Ave. South Park, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 52/22)
  - Thirty-seventh Ave. South Park (Holly Park), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 52/23)
  - 37th Ave. S. Mini Park Outside Basketball Courts, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 52/24)
  - Thomas (mini) Park, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 52/25)
  - Thomas (mini) Park (includes maps), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 52/26)
  - Thomas Mini Park, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 52/27)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trailway, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 52/28)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trail - Acquisition (includes color photographs), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 52/29)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trail - Financial, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 52/30)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trail: Planning Program / Reports Studies ( includes Square Lake ), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 52/31)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trail - Project Description, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 53/1)
  - Thornton Creek Park and Urban Trail: Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 53/2)
  - Thornton Creek and Urban Trail: Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 53/3)
  - Tilikum Place / Chief Sealth Statue, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 53/4)
  - Tilikum Place - Contracts Agreements, 1974 (Box-folder 53/5)
  - Tilikum Place - Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 53/6)
  - Twenty-eighth Jackson / Jackson Street Mini Park (Flo Ware Park), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 53/7)
  - Twenty-sixth Ave. Mini Park / Plum Tree Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 53/8)
  - University District Mini Park, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 53/9)
  - University District Mini Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 53/10)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - Comfort Station / Landscape, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 53/11)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - Urban Park and Recreation Recovery Grant, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 53/12)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - Urban Parks and Recreation Recovery Grant (North), 1980 (Box-folder 53/13)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access Urban Park and Recreation Recovery Program Grant - North, 1981 (Box-folder 53/14)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - North, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 53/15)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - North (Incl. Drawings), 1981-1985 (Box-folder 53/16)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access Project - South, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 53/17)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access Project, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 53/18)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access - South, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 53/19)
  - Urban Recreation Handicapped Access: Bathhouse Theater Volunteer Park, Alki, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 53/20)
  - Urban Recreation Disabled Access - Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 53/21)
  - Urban Trails / Bicycle Paths, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 53/22)
  - Urban Trails / Bicycle Paths, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 53/23)
  - Urban Trails - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 53/24)
  - Van Asselt Community Center Improvements, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 53/25)
  - Van Asselt Community Center, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 53/26)
  - Van Asselt Community Center Gymnasium, 1980 (Box-folder 53/27)
  - Van Asselt Playfield, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 53/28)
  - Sand Point Way Surplus Property, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 54/1)
  - Vandal Watch Program, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 54/2)
  - Victory Heights Playground Rehabilitation, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 54/3)
  - Victory Heights Playground, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 54/4)
  - Victory Heights Playground, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 54/5)
  - View Ridge Playfield, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 54/6)
  - Volunteer Park - Planning, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 54/7)
  - Volunteer Park Phase II Contracts Agreements, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 54/8)
  - Volunteer Park - Planning, 1971 (Box-folder 54/9)
  - Volunteer Park - Master Plan / Richard Haag Associates, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 54/10)
  - Volunteer Park (includes Play Area Traffic Study), 1972 (Box-folder 54/11)
  - Volunteer Park Phase II, 1973 (Box-folder 54/12)
  - Volunteer Park, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 54/13)
  - Volunteer Park Traffic Study, 1975 (Box-folder 54/14)
  - Volunteer Park Traffic Study Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 54/15)
  - Volunteer Park, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 54/16)
  - Volunteer Park Conservatory, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 54/17)
  - Volunteer Park Conservatory, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 54/18)
  - Volunteer Park Conservatory, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 54/19)
  - Volunteer Park Master Plan (includes contracts agreements), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 54/20)
  - Volunteer Park Conservatory Master Plan, 1983 (Box-folder 54/21)
  - Volunteer Park Tennis Conservatory, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 54/22)
  - Volunteer Park Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1983 (Box-folder 54/23)
  - Wallingford Playfield, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 54/24)
  - Wallingford Playfield, 1970 (Box-folder 54/25)
  - Wallingford Playfield, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 54/26)
  - Washington Park Playfield Lighting, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 55/1)
  - Washington Park Playfield, 1976 (Box-folder 55/2)
  - Washington Park Playfield Rehabilitation, 1977 (Box-folder 55/3)
  - Washington Park and Interbay Shelter Rehabilitation, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 55/4)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Corporation Council, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 55/5)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Dedication, 1974 (Box-folder 55/6)